George Korson Collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Sound recordings
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR003)
    - Elijah "Lige" Hale, July 17, 1957
      Brief introduction by Carl Maurer. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Lige Hale, Georgetown Heights, Wadesville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR004)
    - William Jones; John Pierson, July 17, 1957
      Jones and Pierson were interviewed together. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. John B. and Elva Pierson, 105 W. Mahanoy Ave., Mahanoy City, Pennsylvania.
    - Francis Whalen, July 17, 1957
      Recorded at Whalen's home, 133 West Pine St., Mahanoy City, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR005)
    - Clinton Kissawetter, July 17, 1957
      Recorded at Kissawetter's home, 131 South White St., Shenandoah, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR006)
    - Frank Miller, July 19, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Frank Miller, Branchdale, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR007)
    - Charles Solt, July 19, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Solt, 303 Newcastle St., Minersville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR008)
    - David A. Lengle; Mrs. David A. Lengle; Charles "Charlie" Brenner; Mr. Doan, July 21, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. David A. "Dave" Lengle, Molleystown, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania. Doan was from Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
    - Luther Lengle, July 21, 1957
      Son of Mr. and Mrs. David A. "Dave" Lengle. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Luther Lengle, Molleystown, Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR009)
    - Curtis E. "Bull" Maurer; unidentified man does a recitation, July 25, 1957
      Recorded at Maurer's home, Mowry, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR010)
    - William Leib (father-in-law of Glen Zeigenfuse); Glen Zeigenfuse, July 25, 1957
      Carl Maurer did the initial test on the recording. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Glen Zeigenfuse, Lavelle, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR011)
    - Miss Anna Salen; Dr. Harry O. Hoffman, July 31, 1957
      Recorded at Salen's home, Tremont, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR012)
    - Emory Artz, August 1, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Emory Artz, Keffers, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR013)
    - John "Jack" Kline; unidentified Teamster, August 2, 1957
      Recorded at Kline's home, in Hillside, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR014)
    - Joseph "Joe" Boe, August 2, 1957
      Recorded at the carpenter shop, rear of Grand Ave., Tower City, Pennsylvania. Boe lived at 1018 East Grand Ave., Tower City, Pennsylvania.
    - George Lenker, August 2, 1957
      Recorded at the carpenter shop/workshop, rear of Grand Ave., Tower City, Pennsylvania. Pennsylvania Dutch and English are spoken. Lenker lived in Tower City, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR015)
    - Mrs. Dora Birmingham; YWCA girls, August 3, 1957
      Recorded in a hall (possibly a converted barn), Ranch Chickagawi, Sweet Arrow Lake, near Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Mrs. Dora Birmingham is from Frackville; she is daughter of Harry Felter, a miner. AFC 2003/011: SR060 is an abridged version of this recording.
    - John Schneider, August 12, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. John Schneider, 720 Levittown Rd., Lebanon, Pennsylvania. AFC 2003/011: SR058 is an abridged version of this recording.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR016)
    - Al Kutzer, August 15, 1957
      In the interview Kuntzer mentions the framed "Miner's Prayer," and where it hung in the Young Men's Club, its age, etc. He also reads it aloud. Recorded at the Tremont post office, Tremont, Pennsylvania.
    - William A. Stutzman, August 15, 1957
      Mrs. Stutzman and their son Paul were also present and spoke. Recorded at the farmhouse of Mr. and Mrs. William A. Stutzman, Fountain Hegins, RD #2, Hegins Valley, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR017)
    - Theodore Ebert, August 6, 1957
      Recorded at the SPCA Animal Shelter, Pottsville, Pennsylvania. Ebert lived on RD 1, Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR018)
    - Jack Masterson, August 5, 1957
      Recorded at Masterson's home, 304 Wiconisco St., Tower City, Pennsylvania.
    - Harry A. Kuntzleman; Mrs. Harry A. Kuntzleman; William E. Miller; Mrs. Bonnie Reinoehl, August 7, 1957
      Miller is the brother of Mrs. Kuntzleman. Bonnie Reinoehl is the granddaughter of Mrs. Kuntzleman. About 54:07, a discussion about and description of coal carvings. Korson talks about the coal sculpture (dated 1856) that is now in his collection. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Harry A. Kuntzleman, Fourth St., Tower City, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR019)
    - Jacob Lurwick, August 7, 1957
      Recorded at Lurwick's home, 206 Market St., Port Carbon, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR020)
    - Mrs. Arthur Kline, August 9, 1957
      Recorded at Kline's home, RD #2, Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - Miss Mary I. Sherk; Carl Maurer [Morrow]; Luther Spancake, August 9, 1957
      Sherk's name was spelled "Scherk" on the take-up reel. Spancake was a clerk at the station. Recorded at the Reading Railroad Station, Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR021)
    - Walter S. Farquhar, August 8, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Dr. H.O. Hoffman, 1 South 21st St., Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR022)
    - Prof. R.H.H. Aungst, August 3 or 12, 1957
      Recorded at Aungst's home (a farmhouse), Twin Grove, Route #1, near Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR023)
    - Robert W. Snyder, August 28, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Robert W. Snyder, 68 East Pottsville St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - Prof. R.H.H. Aungst, August 28, 1957
      Recorded on the porch of Aungst's home (a farmhouse), Twin Grove, Route #1, near Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - Grant Deaven, August 28, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Grant Deaven, Jonestown, Route #2, Inwood, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR024)
    - Irvin J. Leffler, August 23, 1957
      Continued on SR025-SR026. Recorded at Leffler's home, 56 or 57 South Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview) (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR025)
    - Irvin J. Leffler, August 23, 1957
      Continued from SR024; continued on SR026. Recorded at Leffler's home, 56 or 57 South Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR026)
    - Paul Fidler; Mrs. Paul Fidler; Dr. Clyde Stine, August 10, 1957
      Stine worked at Millersville State Teachers College. Recorded at Paul Fidler's general store, Oak Grove, Pine Grove Township, Pennsylvania.
    - Russell Davies, August 27, 1957
      Recorded at Davies's office, Newkirk Tunnel, one mile west of Tamaqua, Pennsylvania.
    - Irvin J. Leffler, August 28, 1957
      Continued from SR025. Leffler spoke in Pennsylvania Dutch. Recorded at Leffler's home, 56 or 57 South Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR027)
    - Dr. Fred L. Herring; Mrs. Fred L. Herring; Dr. H. O. Hoffman, August 20, 1957
      Dr. H.O. Hoffman is from Pottsville. Recorded at the home of Dr. and Mrs. Herring, Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR028)
    - Prof. Bruce L. Christ, August 23, 1957
      Continued on SR029. Recorded at Bruce Christ's home, 77 1/2 Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR029)
    - Prof. Bruce L. Christ, August 29, 1957
      Continued from SR028. Recorded at Bruce Christ's home, 77 1/2 Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR030)
    - Mrs. Oren G. Umholtz, August 21, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Squire and Mrs. Oren G. Umholtz, Valley View, Pennsylvania.
    - Mrs. Clinton M. Otto; also, possibly Mr. Stutzman, August 21, 1957
      Recorded on the porch at Otto's home, Fountain, Hegins, RD #2, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR031)
    - J. Benson Adams, August 27, 1957
      Recorded in the board room, Summit Hill Trust Company Bank, Summit Hill, Carbon County, Pennsylvania.
    - Charles H. Cunningham, August 27, 1957
      Recorded in Cunningham's shop. He lived at 27 West White St., Summit Hill, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR032)
    - Lee E. Schrope, August 24, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Lee E. Schrope, Hegins, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR033)
    - Frank W. Houser; Mrs. Frank Houser, August 30, 1957
      Recorded in the garden, at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Frank W. Houser, 125 East Broad St., Williamstown, Dauphin County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR034)
    - Dr. Daniel I. Sultzbach, September 3, 1957
      Sultzbach was a minister; his name was given as "Rev. Dr. Sultzbach" on the take-up reel. Recorded at the home of Dr. and Mrs. D.I. Sultzbach, 2226 Tilman St., Allentown, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview, part 1), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR035)
    - Arthur H. Henninger, September 5, 1957
      Henninger was superintendent of Schuylkill County schools. Recorded at his office.
  - Sound recording (interviews, part 2), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR035)
    - Paul Lengel; John Haas, September 5, 1957
      A small amount of the next interview can be heard at end of this recording, recorded at a different speed. Recorded at Lengel's farmhouse, Pine Grove, #1, Pennsylvania.
    - Ralph Kantner, September 5, 1957
      Interview continued on SR036. Recorded at Kantner's home, 62 North Main St., Pine Grove, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR036)
    - Ralph Kantner, September 5, 1957
      Interview continued from SR035. Recorded at Kantner's home, 62 North Main St., Pine Grove, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR037)
    - William H. Adams, September 6, 1957
      Recorded at Adams's home, Zerbe Post Office, Zerbe, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR038)
    - Mrs. Anna Lucretia Daubert Green, September 9, 1957
      This recording is duplicated in part on SR058. Recorded at the Pine Grove office of the West Schuylkill Press. Green lived at 4 Cherry St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - John Hampton Haldeman, September 9, 1957
      Recorded at Haldeman's drugstore, 136 South Tulpehocken St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - George Gordon Adams, September 9, 1957
      Recorded at Adams's home, 280 South Main St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR039)
    - Elmer "Jerry" Wetzel, September 20, 1957
      Recorded at the barroom of William Boyd Sr. and William Boyd Jr., Donaldson, Frailey Township, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR040)
    - Charles H. Harner, September 6, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Florence Minnich (Charles Harner's niece), 14 Union St., Tremont, Pennsylvania. Harner lived at Shamokin, RD #1, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR041)
    - L.D. Lamont, September 23, 1957
      Recorded in the basement, Pottsville Free Public Library, Pottsville, Pennsylvania. Lamont lived at 1923 West Norwegian St., Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR042)
    - Lincoln English; Mrs. Lincoln English, September 18, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Lincoln, Donaldson, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR043)
    - Edith Patterson, September 21, 1957
      Recorded at Patterson's home, 714 Mahantongo St., Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR044)
    - William W. Lewis, September 29, 1957
      Recorded at Trevorton High School, 701 Shamokin St., Trevorton, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR045)
    - Clara R. Wertz [Mrs. Henry E. Wertz], October 2, 1957
      Recorded at Wertz's general store, Lincoln, near Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR046)
    - William Breiner; Harvey L. Snider; Gertrude Snider [Mrs. Harvey L. Snider], October 1, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Harvey L. Snider (Mrs. Snider is Breiner's daughter), Straus Valley, West Penn Township, Carbon County, Pennsylvania.
    - Edward Redline, October 1, 1957
      Recorded in the board room, Summit Hill Trust Company, 2 East Ludlow St., Summit Hill, Pennsylvania. Redline lived in the apartment above the bank.
  - Sound recording (interviews, part 1), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR047)
    - Walter [S.?] Farquhar, September 12, 1957
      The name is spelled "Farquar" on the original take-up reel. Recorded in the basement, Pottsville Free Public Library, Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
    - Edith Haas [Mrs. William Haas], September 23, 1957
      Recorded in the basement, Pottsville Free Public Library, Pottsville, Pennsylvania. Haas lived at 560 Sunbury St., Minersville, Pennsylvania.
    - Stanley Achenbach, September 23, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Stanley Achenbach, 78 High St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania.
    - Harry C. Jennings, October 4, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Harry C. Jennings, 60 Schuylkill St., Cressona, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview, part 2), 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR047)
    - Mrs. Walter Lash; Frank Troutman, September 12, 1957
      Frank Troutman is Mrs. Lash's father. Recorded at the home of Mrs. Walter Lash, 324 Laurel St., Minersville, Schuylkill County, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR048)
    - William "Stuff" Williams; Elwood "Woodie" Reese, September 24, 1957
      Recorded at City Hall, Lansford, Pennsylvania. Williams lived at 35 Coal St., Lansford, Pennsylvania.
    - Miss Rosemarie Boyle, October 15, 1957
      Identified as Mrs., not Miss, on the original take-up reel. Recording continued on SR049. Recorded at Hazleton Public Library, Hazleton, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR049)
    - Milton G. Schwenk, September 7, 1957
      Recorded at Schwenk's home, 1 Pleasant Row, Schuylkill Haven, Pennsylvania.
    - Miss Rosemarie Boyle, October 15, 1957
      See note for AFC 2003/011: SR048. Recording continued from SR048. Recorded at Hazleton Public Library, Hazleton, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR050)
    - Mary Moran [Mrs. Francis Moran]; Mrs. Nellie McDonald, October 2, 1957
      McDonald is Mrs. Moran's mother. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Francis Moran, 111 Third St., Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
    - Miss E. Louise Bigler, October 5, 1957
      Recorded at Pottsville Free Public Library, Pottsville, Pennsylvania. Bigler lived at 302 Fairview St., Pottsville, Pennsylvania.
    - Lewis Coskey, October 8, 1957
      Recorded at Coskey's workshop, Pikes Peak, Sweet Valley, near Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR051)
    - Mrs. Walter Lash; Frank Troutman, September 18, 1957
      See note for AFC 2003/011: SR047 (part 2). Recorded at home of Mrs. Walter Lash, 324 Laurel St., Minersville, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR052)
    - Ray Evelan; introduced by Max Rosenblatt, October 13, 1957
      Rosenblatt is Rae Korson's brother (George Korson's brother-in-law). Recorded at home of Mr. and Mrs. Ray Evelan, Noxen, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview, part 1), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 3 3/4 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR053)
    - C. Edgar Patience; introduced by Max Rosenblatt, October 6, 1957
      See note for AFC 2003/011: SR053, part 1. Part of SR053 can be heard at the end of the recording. Recorded at Patience's home, 82 Looma St., Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview, part 2), 1 sound tape reel: analog; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR053)
    - C. Edgar Patience, October 6, 1957
      Recorded at Patience's home, 82 Looma St., Wilkes-Barre, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR054)
    - A. Feeley [and George Korson], March 31, 1957
      Continued on AFC 2003/011: SR055-SR056. Recorded at the studio of the American National Red Cross, Washington, D.C. Feeley lived in New Philadelphia, Pennsylvania.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR055)
    - A. Feeley [and George Korson], March 31, 1957
      Continued from AFC 2003/011: SR054, and continued on AFC 2003/011: SR056. See notes for SR054.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR056)
    - A. Feeley [and George Korson], March 31, 1957
      Continued from AFC 2003/011: SR054-SR055. See notes for SR054.
  - Sound recording (interview), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR057)
    - A. Feeley [and George Korson], March 31, 1957
      See notes for AFC 2003/011: SR054.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR058)
    - John Schneider, August 12, 1957
      The surname is spelled "Snyder" on the take-up reel. Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. John Schneider, 720 Levittown Rd., Lebanon, Pennsylvania. Dub copy. See AFC 2003/011: SR015.
    - Charles Kimmel, August 13, 1957
      Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR061.
    - Dr. Arthur H. Henninger, September 5, 1957
      Henninger was superintendent of Schuylkill County schools. Recorded at his office. Duplicated from AFC 2003/011: SR035.
    - Fred L. Herring; Mrs. Fred L. Herring, August 20, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Mr. and Mrs. Herring, Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Duplicated from AFC 2003/011: SR027.
    - Mrs. Anna Lucretia Daubert Green, September 9, 1957
      Recorded at the Pine Grove office of the West Schuylkill Press. Green lived at 4 Cherry St., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Duplicated from AFC 2003/011: SR038.
    - Mrs. Walter Lash, September 18, 1957
      324 Laurel St., Minersville, Pennsylvania. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR062.
    - William "Pop" Sholley, October 5, 1957
      Continued on AFC 2003/011: SR059. Recorded at the home of Ralph M. Hyle, "Fair Winds," Bird Hill Rd., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Sholley lived in Lebanon, Pennsylvania. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR065.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR059)
    - William "Pop" Sholley, August 12, 1957
      Continued from AFC 2003/011: SR058. Recorded at the home of Ralph M. Hyle (spelled "Kyle" on the take-up reel), "Fair Winds," Bird Hill Rd., Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Sholley lived in Lebanon, Pennsylvania. Dub copy. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR061.
    - Albert B. "Abby" Morgan, August 27, 1957
      Recorded at the office of the Inside Superintendent of the Newkirk Tunnel. Morgan lived at 438 East Broad St., Tamaqua, Pennsylvania. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR065.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR060)
    - Mrs. Dora Birmingham; YWCA girls, August 3, 1957
      Recorded at Ranch Chickagawi, Sweet Arrow Lake, near Pine Grove, Pennsylvania. Birmingham was from Frackville, Pennsylvania. Dub copy. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR015.
    - Haas, Charles Henry "Mule," September 22, 1957
      Recorded at the home of John Mayers, Llewellyn Rd., Minersville, Pennsylvania. Haas also lived on Llewellyn Rd., Minersville, Pennsylvania. Duplicated in abridged version from AFC 2003/011: SR063.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR061)
    - Kimmel, Charles, August 13, 1957
      Recorded at the home of Dr. Harry Hoffman, Pottsville, Pennsylvania. Kimmel was from Keffers, Pennsylvania.
    - Albert B. "Abby" Morgan, August 27, 1957
      Recorded at the office of the Inside Superintendent of the Newkirk Tunnel. Morgan lived at 438 East Broad St., Tamaqua, Pennsylvania. AFC 2003/011: SR059 contains an abridged version of this recording.
  - Sound recording (interviews), 1 sound tape reel: analog, 7 1/2 ips; 7 in. (Item-id AFC 2003/011: SR062)
    - Michael J. Burke, September 12, 1957